本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 小癫羊 带着猫咪私奔 华青墨 许块块
校对： 许块块   后期： 唱唱反调
戴森我只是...我只是很不安
I'm just... I'm getting restless, Dyson.
我记得的最后一件事是我被带出了戴尔
The last thing I remember is being taken from the Dal,
醒来的时候就在树林里
then waking up in the woods.
我不能一直躲着等待答案
I can't keep hiding, waiting for answers.
在尤那达人人安定下来之前先保持低调吧
Gotta lay low until the Una Mens settle down.
所以他们想让我死 排队! 拿号!
So they want me dead. Line up! Take a number!
恭喜加入啊! 还要我继续吗?
Welcome to the club! Should I keep going?
波 这比你想象的严重
This is bigger than you think, Bo.
尤那达人人的力量来自远古
The Una Mens power is ancient.
不听不听
Dun dun dun.
- 我很严肃地 - 抱歉
- I'm serious. - I'm sorry.
但是幻想委员会? 古老条例?
But fancy councils? Ye old rules?
这些是我脑中最不愿想的事
It's just, it's the last thing on my mind.
你想谈谈你脑中最想的事吗?
You want to talk about that first thing on your mind?
- ...有消息吗? - 最近没有
- ...any word? - Not lately.
但是她处于未知 安全远离是最好的
But it's better that she stays away safe with all of these unknowns.
劳伦很聪明 她可以自行解决
Lauren's smart, she can handle herself.
好吧 既然我得保护我自己
Well, since I have to protect myself
远离未知...
from all these unknowns...
应该换我被打了 腰带往下哦
I should get a hit. Below the belt.
你有些不一样了哦
Something is different about you.
这个嘛...你看起来很喜欢 疯狂喜欢
Well... you seem to like it. In a huge way.
- 那是什么? - 我不知道 旧管道?
- What was that? - I don't know. Old pipes?
当你不知你是谁时 生活会很艰辛
Life is hard when you don't  know who you are.
当你知道真相后 生活会更艰难
It's harder when you don't know what you are.
我的爱伴随着死亡的降临
My love carries a death sentence.
我迷失了多年
I was lost for years...
在藏匿中找寻
searching, while hiding.
那个不为人知的属于我的世界
Only to find that I belong to a world hidden from humans.
但我已厌倦躲藏
I won't hide anymore.
我要过自己想要的生活
I will live the life I choose.
- 好了 少喝烈酒 多翘屁股!- 嗷嗷
- All right, less hooch, more tooch! - Owww-owww...
好了 好了 最后一下 呼吸 呼吸
Okay, okay, one more knot. Just breathe, just breathe.
好了 好了
There you go. There you go.
完事了 天哪 还不是一股
Done. God, not a single strand.
我跳完电臀舞了 我能吃点奶酪泡芙吗?
I'm done twerking out. Can I have Cheezies?
- 是的 你可以吃点 - 谢谢
- Yes, you can have Cheezies. - Thank you.
呃!
Ugh!
肯吉 特里克的异基尼斯防护又出毛病了
Kenz, Trick's Ignis Rim is acting up again.
呃 我来了! 抱歉 我可能设定错了
Ugh, coming! Sorry, I probably just set it up wrong.
它应该只能阻挡邪恶的异种
It's only supposed to block out malicious Fae.
你回来真是太好了
Oh, I'm so glad you're home.
过来
Come here.
你闻起来像是汗淋淋的健身男 但是我不介意
You smell like sweaty gym-dude and I don't even care.
嗯 肯吉我走了一小时了并不是我在意
Uh, Kenz, I've been gone an hour. And not that I mind,
但是这个持续拥抱还要多久?
but how long is this incessant hugging gonna last?
只要能让你忘了你离开过
As long as it takes to forget you were ever gone.
来点奶酪泡芙?
Cheezie?
不 我挺好的 已经吃过了
No. I'm good, I already ate.
戴森和我只是...
Dyson and I just...
别在小-朋-友 瓦-科-基面前说
Oh! Not in front of the B-A-B-Y  V-A-L-K... E?
- 或者是 Y? - 我不是小孩了!
- Or is it, Y? - I'm not a baby!
我已经两周大了 谢谢
I'm almost two weeks old. Thank you.
好吧 小孩 你想起你为谁工作了吗?
All right, tweener 'tude. You remember who you work for yet?
我告诉你了 我不记得
I already told you, I don't remember.
这是个人隐私 好吗?
It's called a previous life, okay?
到目前为止 我所知道的就是我是黑暗
So far, all I know is that I'm Dark.
这让我觉得你知道的比告诉我的多
Which makes me think you know more than you're telling me...
你懂的 这个年龄的孩子 还能干啥?
Oh, you know, kids this age. Whaddya gonna do?
你知道吗? 俱乐部封锁了管他呢
You know what? Screw club house arrest.
嗯!我们出去吧
Mm! Let's go out.
那这里的奶酪泡芙小孩怎么办?
What about Cheezie breath over here?
嘿 小'T
Hey, Lil' T.
你想一起来吗? 很无聊 一点也不好玩
Do you wanna come out with us? Totally boring, not fun.
或者你想呆在这个安全的边缘带里
Or do you want to stay in safety rim zone
并且再看一遍X档案?
and watch the X-Files again?
X档案? 当然!
X-Files. Yes!
- 成交 - 嗯!
- Done. - Mm!
... 饮料! 耶!
... drinks! Yeah!
为我们干杯
Drink to us.
嗯 就像这里占领了法国一样
Mmm. It is like occupied France in here.
怎么音乐这么悲伤?
What's with the cry tunes?
尤那达人人来到镇上了 一切一切都关闭了
Una Mens come to town, errrrything shut down.
好吧 我希望来一个真正的夜不归宿
Yeah well, I was hoping for a real night out.
好吧 抱歉 春假小姐
Well, sorry Miss Spring Breaker.
我向戴森保证了我会带你到安全的地方
I promised Dyson I'd take you somewhere safe.
哦! 你记得那团绑架我
Oh! You remember a cloud of black smoke
到这里的黑雾 对吗?
kidnapped me here, right?
是的
Right.
我们是否知道关于这个浪人的什么...
Do we know anything about this Wander...
...呃 我不想讨论这个话题
... Ahhh. I don't feel like talking about it.
我想跳舞
I wanna dance.
玩真的?　在这? 萨德威勒里?
Are you for real? Right here? In Sadville?
现在就像了
Now that is more like it.
波波回来啦
Bobo returns.
还带了特别福利...?
With bonus features...?
嘿!
Hey!
- 你带了吗? - 我来的太匆忙
- Did you bring it? - I'm in a rush.
什么? 样品诱卖?
What? Flip flop sample sale?
我受够了幼儿玩具 现在是卡车卖场
I'm done with the kiddy toys. It's Tonka Truck time.
你做梦也买不起永久能量
You can't even dream to afford for permanent powers.
你也不能负担得起我供货的东西
You can't even pay me for what I supply.
等着瞧吧 你会拿到支付的
Look, you will get paid...
马西莫 只要我的能量不衰退
as soon as my powers stop fading. Massimo.
肯吉? 波?
Kenzi? Bo?
...Mulder? 斯克里?
...Mulder? Scully?
哦天哪 你们在这干什么?
Oh my god, what are you doing here?
# 这是个完整的故事 #
So here's a story from A-to-Z
# 仔细听 跟上我 #
you wanna get with me you gotta listen carefully
# 恩姆在这里 爱你显而易见 #
We got Em in the place who likes it in your face.
# G像主持人 乐在其中 #
We got G like MC who likes it on an. Easy V doesn't
# V不会免费上门 她是正牌淑女 #
come for free. She's a real lady,
# 至于我 可看到 #
as for me, ah you'll see.
# 砰然倒地 吹向四方 #
Slam your body down and wind it all around.
Slam your body down and wind it all around!
# 欲成我真爱 #
If you wanna be my lover.
# 先拢我挚友 先拢我挚友 #
You gotta get with my friends. You gotta get with my friends.
# 使友谊固若金汤 恒久不变 #
Make it last forever friendships never end...
惊喜! 你会发疯吗?
Surprise! Are you so mad?
事实上 这太惊人了!
Actually, that was freakin' incredible!
变坏的感觉真好
It feels so good to be bad.
肯吉 我们被打劫了
Kenzi. We've been robbed.
塔米辛
Tamsin.
我觉得我又长大了
I think I grew again.
有人在我们家里 陌生人!
People were in our home. Strangers!
而且是对旧家具有特殊品味的陌生人
Strangers with great taste in thrift shop furniture.
你想让我给你什么吗?
Would you like me to get you something?
一杯咖啡或者一张休息的椅子?
A coffee or chair to break?
我会干掉做这件事的人
I'm gonna break whoever did this.
我们家还有个孩子!
We had a child in the home!
类似孩子吧 会不会是尤那达人人?
Sort of. Ugh, could this be Una Mens?
不 他们不是小偷
No, they're not thieves.
他们对物质财产没兴趣
Material possessions don't interest them.
但是也许这跟异种毫无关系
But maybe this isn't Fae-related at all.
也许只是非法侵入
Maybe it's just a good old break and enter.
如果那个边界去掉了 人类依然可以进入
If that rim was up, humans could still enter.
无论是不是异种
Fae or not,
没人会进入我的房子拿走我的东西
no one comes into my house and takes what's mine.
你懂 如果你待会需要放松
You know, if you need to unwind later,
我们可以 呃...
we could, uh...
- 逛街 - 对啊 逛街
- Go shopping. - Go shopping, yeah.
好吧 如果你感觉还不错 你可以随便逛
Well, if you're good, you can go in all the stores.
好吧 如果你感觉不错 我会刷爆你的卡
Well if you're good, I'll max out your credit cards.
- 两倍 - 我可以来吗?
- Twice. - Can I come?
我会列出可疑名单再追踪
I've got a suspicious lead to track.
- 让我帮你吧 - 你已经在帮忙了
- Let me help. - Oh, you already are.
当我从设施那回来时 我会解释的
I'll explain when I get back from the facilities!
波! 浴室在...另一边
Bo! The bathroom is... the other way.
并且...我在照顾小孩
And... I'm babysitting.
那个女孩是谁?
Who's that girl?
走失人员 我们需要找到她
Someone who's lost. And you and I need to find her.
这都是我的错 我相信了他们
This is all my fault. I believed them...
他们告诉我不会伤害你
They told me they wouldn't hurt you.
他们是谁?
Who are "they"?
你好 好久不见 劳伦
Hello. Long time no see, Lauren.
或者我该叫你...Karen
Or should I call you... Karen.
来吧 马西莫
Come on, Massimo.
我要解禁钱包 我正觊觎一双鞋
I've got wallets to lift; shoes to covet...
噢! 干什么?!
Ow! What the hell?!
嘿!!
Hey!!
好吧 我平时的轿车和大杯摩卡冰拿铁呢?
Okay, where's my usual SUV and Venti-Mocha-Iced-latte?
那些不付钱的顾客是没有会员待遇的
No VIP treatment for customers that don't pay.
他要给你颜色看看
He's sending a message.
那你...你告诉他
Well you... you give a message that
他把拉链拉好放他的小德鲁伊附近...
he can take this zip tie and put it around his tiny druid...
有人吗 发生什么事
Hello?! What's happening?
没事了 波
Three-nothing, Bo.
那我们东西 我可不会让你带走肯吉
Take our things, but you will not take my Kenzi.
跟你还跟对了
Uh, followed you just in time, sketch bag.
- 来吧 - 谢谢你
- Come on. - Oh. Thank you!
- 救了我 - 肯吉
- For saving me! - Kenz.
什么时候你开始单飞了
Since when do you fly solo, huh?
我回来了 我们重回以前了
I'm back, we're back,
小孩也回来了 一起回归啊
baby got back. Together-like.
我认识这些人 我叫他们来的
Look, I know these guys. Like, called them know them.
什么 你现在喜欢被绑起来了
What? You're into getting zip-tied now?
不 我知道谁抢了我们
No, I know who robbed us.
而且都是我的错 我会弥补的
But it's my problem and I can handle it.
是我们的问题 让我们把东西拿回来吧
Hey, it's our problem. Let's get our shit back.
- 话说这人谁啊 - 马西莫
- So who is this guy, anyway? - Massimo.
- 德鲁伊马西莫? - 你知道他?
- Druid Massimo? - You know him?
没错 他烂透了
Yeah, I do. And he sucks.
诡异的德鲁伊
... creepy druid.
波 对未知举步维艰?
Bo. Tough times in parts unknown?
这你可是想不起来的
Not that you would remember.
你的神秘玻璃药剂撒到地上了
Your rune glass potion fell flat.
我可不这么想
Yeah, I'm not so sure that it did.
谢谢你亲吻的封印
Thanks to the seal from your kiss.
什么神秘玻璃药剂
Rune-glass-potion-what-now?
我要知道我有能力
I like to know when I'm sealing something.
他给塔米辛药剂来杀我
He gave Tamsin a potion to kill me.
其实是标记你 允许你超出平面
Actually, to mark you. Allow you to transcend planes;
被收集
to be collected.
是个双保险 以防塔米辛反悔
An insurance policy in case Tamsin didn't pan out.
她死了真可惜啊
It's a shame that she died.
悲剧 谁带我走的?
Tragic. Who took me?
不幸的是 我只是受雇送货的
Unfortunately, I was just hired to deliver the goods.
肯定我能告诉你点什么
There must be something I can tell you...
没有 一无所知
Nah. There's nothing.
接下来是这样 你把我们东西还回来
Well here's how this is gonna go: you're gonna give us our stuff back
并且不许再招惹肯吉
and then you're gonna leave Kenzi alone.
她不需要你的服务了
She won't be requiring your services any longer.
她的欠债可未还清
That doesn't settle her debt.
没有吗? 给你一脚见钱眼开
No? How about a knee to your euro-sack?
好的好的 让我们像成人一样解决问题嘛
Okay, okay why don't we just handle this like adults?!
异种 德鲁伊 人类 一起来
Fae, Druid, human ... comin' together.
地球和平 我们是世界啊
Peace on Earth. We are the world.
- 什么的 - 我有提议
- Kind of... stuff. - I have a proposal.
现在又想3P了是嘛
Mm, here comes the threesome request.
好主意 留下次吧
Let's bank the trio idea 'til next time.
日本猪毛菜苏打草药 十分罕见
The Japanese Salsola Soda herb. It's very rare.
我听说长在光明派异种医生的绿墙里
But I hear it grows on the Light Fae Doctor's green wall.
- 你想让我去劳伦那里? - 你认识她?
- You want me to go to Lauren's? - Do you know her?
你帮我拿来 我们两清
You get it for me, and we're even.
杰拉尔丁?
Geraldine?
我要把这个拿回去 我们的东西呢?
I'm taking this back. What about our stuff?
我没烧的都让你拿回去
You'll get back what I haven't burnt.
相信我 帮你们大忙了
Did you a favour, trust me.
那些口音桌子?
Those accent tables?
好吧 我们帮你拿草药
Fine. We'll get you the herb.
要是你食言不兑现
But if you don't hold up your end of the bargain,
我就杀了你
I'll kill you.
我的梳子? 你留着吧
And my hairbrush? You can keep.
一点也不诡异...
Because that's not creepy at all...
我们被监视了
We're being watched.
你找到我了 现在怎样
You found me. Now what?
防水布一号下面是什么
What's behind tarp number one?
他们想让我们看
They want us to look.
玩他们的游戏 我不玩了
Play their little game. I'm done playing.
- 我跟你睡了 - 克里斯朵
- I slept with you... - Oh crystal.
不
No.
因为他们逼我的 跟你亲密
Because they made me. To keep you close.
可是之后 我 我不知道
But then, after I did... I ... I don't know.
那样特别 你知道吗 有感情了
It was different, you know? It was more.
- 间谍床戏 - 我有错过什么吗
- Ahh. Spy-banged. - Did I miss something?
我曾来过这
I've been here before.
其实 跟你处境一样
In your shoes, actually.
我有个兄弟
I have a brother.
我唯一的兄弟 不可分离
My only sibling. We were inseparable.
我们一起想改变世界
Together, we were going to change the world.
- 听着不错 - 确实不错
- Sounds nice. - Yeah, yeah it was.
可后来变了
Until it wasn't anymore.
我们改变世界的方法是
Our version of changing the world turned into
用炸弹炸毁管道
blowing up pipelines using pipe bombs.
十一位丧生
Eleven people died.
你是恐怖分子?
You're a terrorist?
那里应该没有人的
Nobody was supposed to be there...
我因此每天恨自己 酿成惨祸
Not a day goes by that I don't hate myself for what happened.
- 不是你的错 - 我做的炸药
- It wasn't your fault. - I made the explosives.
让我兄弟保管了
And then I trusted my brother with them.
他现在在哪?
Where is he now?
重点是 凯伦逃跑了
Point is, is that Karen ran.
自那以后 我一直在逃
And I have been running ever since.
我不懂为什么跟你说这个
I don't even know why I'm telling you this.
我永远不会告诉波的
I never even told Bo.
感人肺腑 现在 看防水布后面
Moving story. Now, look under the tarp.
我猜我玩的游戏还没结束
I guess I'm not done playing games just yet.
长老需要你一小时内出诊断
An elder needs your diagnosis within the hour.
否则克里斯朵死
Or Crystal dies.
这根本不是环保狂 根本就是光明派异种胡来
This isn't about eco terrorism. This is Light Fae bullshit.
我试着理解 肯吉 真的
I'm trying to understand, Kenz, really, I am.
你为什么会找那个烂人?
Why would you ever go to that nutbag?
我受够让别人对我指手画脚了
I was tired of everyone telling me to "go".
我那也不想去 我想跟你战斗
I don't want to "go" anywhere. I want to fight with you.
你是啊 你一直都跟我并肩作战
But you do. You always have.
我以为会很简单的好么
Look, I thought it'd be simple, you know.
去找马西莫 做个交易
Go see Massimo. Make a deal.
成为异种 可到头来还是有时效的
Become Fae. But it turned out to be temporary.
- 就闪点火光 - 花了你多少?
- And a little on the chintzy side. - How much did it cost you?
再一点草药 亲爱的
One more herb, baby.
太爽了 这些都看起来一样啊
Phew! Well I'm glad these all look identical.
当你需要劳伦的时候她在哪
Where's Lauren when you need her?
情伤了?
Ex nostalgia attack?
整件塔夫特的事还是困扰我
You know, this whole Taft thing still baffles me.
劳伦很聪明 我是说 也许她没被骗
I mean, Lauren is smart! I mean, maybe she wasn't tricked.
也许她愿意为他工作 从他那里获利?
Maybe she wanted to work for him, you know, get something from him?
- 养老保险? - 我不知道
- Like... a pension? - I don't know.
显而易见 我们的关系建立在
Apparently the foundation of our entire relationship
一无所知之上
was based on "not knowing".
不管值不值得
Well, look, for whatever it's worth
我想劳伦是好人
I think that Lauren's one of the good ones.
我一直以为你站在戴森这边
I always thought you were on Dyson.
在? 什么在? 你什么意思
On? What... what on? What do you mean?
你懂嘛 狼群 这是什么
Oh, you know, Team Wolf. What is this?
是真的 她的名字不叫劳伦
It's true. Her name is not Lauren.
是卡伦 卡伦・碧蒂
It's Karen. Karen Beattie.
听起来一点也不性感
Okay, not the sexiest moniker.
秒懂她为什么改名了
Kinda get why she might have changed it.
我不认识她
I didn't know her.
拜托 宝贝 不会的
Come on babe, that's not true.
会的 我甚至不知道她的名字
No, I don't even know her name!
现在她也许又换了新名字
And now she's probably changed it again.
开始了新生活 在安全的地方...
Started a new, better life. Somewhere safe...
远离我
away from me.
你还好吧
Look, you okay over there?
好啊 在我前任的家里逛
Oh, yeah. Just hangin' in my ex's apartment.
找奇怪的东西 我没事
Finding weird shit. I'm fine.
为什么我生命中的人都要对我撒谎?
What is it that makes everyone in my life lie to me?
除了你 也正是我爱你的原因
Except for you. That's why I love you.
- 天啊 我找到了 - 爱你没错啊
- Oh my god, I found it! - Ah, also why I love you.
- 你防护那门了吗 - 没有
- Did you rim the door? - No.
异基尼斯防护 特里克提过
Ignis Rim Converterent. Trick mentioned this.
不是不让异种进入 而是不许外出
Instead of keeping Fae out, it locks them in.
马西莫一定见过我们的
Massimo must have seen ours...
他变态指数大大飙升啊
And he just graduated from a-hole to douche.
好了 让我过吧
Okay, let me try crossing.
警告 我的夹克可是高燃物
Warning: My poly-blend jacket is highly flammable.
一跃而过 宝贝 一跃而过
Drop and roll, baby. Drop and roll.
好的 好的
Okay, okay...
天啊 真他妈的疼
Ah! Oh god! It stings like a mother!
马西莫玩的哪出?
What sick game is Massimo playing?
- 嘿 - 戴森 猜怎么着?
- Hey. - Dyson. Guess what?
我找的劳伦的语音信箱和俱乐部号八次诶!
I found Lauren's voicemail and the clubhouse number eight times!
你觉得赞吧 没错哦
Are you impressed? Yeah you are.
他的最后一通电话是两天前
His last call was two days ago.
我去调出高速路沿线的所有办公
I'm gonna pull records from all businesses
和公用电话的记录
and pay phones along that highway.
准备好更多的荧光笔
Get ready for more highlighting.
好重啊 我曾是个好警察吗
Oh. This is heavy. Was I a good cop?
你很硬派
You were tough.
心情不好的时候 你可是个魔鬼
On a bad day, you could be a real... monster.
你觉得我很可怕
You think I'm hideous!
连强盗看到我都会被吓跑
Even the robbers ran away when they saw my face!
我说的魔鬼是夸你呢 好吗
I meant monster in a good way, okay?
这根本就说不通
That doesn't even make sense!
嘘 拜托
Shh! Please.
- 波是你的女朋友吗 - 不 不是
- Is Bo your girlfriend? - No. She is not.
但是你想让她做你女朋友吗
But do you want her to be?
我曾经想...
I did...
后来树上有个姑娘带走了我的爱
but then a lady in a tree took my love away.
等我回来的时候 波已经有女朋友了
And by the time I got it back, Bo had a girlfriend.
你忘记开头说'从前'了
You forgot to start with 'once upon a time'.
从前...我们从没在对的时间相遇 没了
Once upon a time... we never found the right time. The End.
爱一个人是什么感觉
What does love feel like?
我们真的要谈这个吗
Are we really doing this?
等你感受到的时候 你就懂了
When you feel it, you'll know it.
当爱情消逝 你再也不会想失去它
And when it's gone, you'll never want to lose it again.
知道吗 去找波和肯吉谈这事吧 好吗
You know what, talk to Bo and Kenzi about this stuff, okay?
我真的不擅长这个
It's really not my bag.
我不能去找波谈
I can't talk to Bo.
因为我是黑暗派的 她讨厌我
She hates me because I'm Dark.
好吧 每人都有自己的选择
Well, everyone makes a choice.
除了我 那是之前的我选的
Not me. It was the me before me.
好吧 也许哪天你能做出更好的选择
Well, maybe someday you'll get to make a better choice.
也许不能 反正这不是我的问题
Maybe not. It's not my problem.
为什么你要那么刻薄
Why do you have to be so mean?!
为什么你有那么多问题
Why do you have so many questions?!
我无法相信他用肯吉的方法证明了
I can't believe he Kenzi-proofed it.
他在利用我的力量牵制我
He's playing off my power.
怎么才能让你不放火花
How do we make you stop sparking?
只能等它用完了
Ugh, it kinda just runs out.
你知道 就像防晒霜一样 游完泳得再涂一次
You know, like sunscreen. Reapply after swimming.
我想我可以去洗个澡
I guess I can take a shower...
但是...我真的不想把头发弄湿了
but I... I really don't want to get my hair wet.
- 真是种折磨 - 我听见了
- It's an ordeal. - I hear ya.
不过 你知道 已经一星期了
You know what though, it's been a week.
也许我该把它洗掉了
I probably should wash it.
劳伦的护发素是最差的吗
Is Lauren's conditioner the worst?
它就是最差的
It's the worst.
它里面含不含有保湿剂的啊
Does it even contain humectants?
天知道那女人抹些什么在头发上
God knows what that woman puts in her hair.
真不能相信她
She cannot be trusted.
我不知道你怎么样 不过我喜欢桃子的洗发水
I don't know about you I need a little peach in my shampoo.
- 好清醒 - 好样的
- Refreshing. - Attagirl.
现在 如果唯一能除掉那边的人
Now, if the only one who can remove a rim
就是设立它的人...
is the one who set it...
不 我们弄乱它
No, we have to scramble it.
我需要一面帕库镜子和一只怪物眼睛
One Pakua Mirror and ogre eye, required.
难道我是新的特里克吗
Am I the new Trick?
你能找到所有这些东西吗
Can you get all that stuff?
你难道不知道我是谁吗
Have you met me?
好的 我会救你的
Okay, I'm gonna save your ass.
忘记特里克吧 我是新的波
Forget Trick, I'm the new Bo!
好
Okay.
谢谢你给我爱的自由
"For giving me the freedom to love."
我确实给了
And I do.
谁在那儿?
Who's there?
...浪人吗
...Wanderer?
你以为我会让你再次把我带走吗?
If you think that I'm gonna let you take me again?
那你就找错淫妖了
You are messing with the wrong Succubus!
我来了我来了 我来了
I'm here I'm here I'm here.
异基尼斯防护失灵
Ignis adflicto affligo.
我成功了 耶
I did it! Yes!
- 波 发生什么了 - 你看见了吗
- Bo, what happened? - Did you see it?
我怎么了
What's happening to me?
都是我的错
This is all my fault.
不 不是
No, it's not.
你怎么会知道他把什么关在笼子里了
How could you know what he kept in that cage?
- 波 听我说 - 我会处理好这事的
- Bo, listen to me... - I'm gonna take care of this.
我欠他的 马西莫 欠他很多
I owe him! Massimo. A lot.
我一直在偷东西来偿还他
Okay, and I've been stealing to pay him.
- 肯吉- 从特里克那偷的
- Kenz. - From Trick!
- 肯吉! - 还有从黑尔那儿
- Kenzi! - And from Hale.
我给了他查姆拉细枝
I gave him the Twig of Zamora.
你疯了吗 等等 我都不知道那是什么
Are you crazy!? Wait, I don't know what that is.
他就一直不停地索取索取
And he just keeps taking and taking
可对获得永恒的力量来说还是不够
and it's still not enough for a permanent power.
但我必须得做点什么 人类在被带走 波
But I had to do something. Claimed humans are being taken, Bo!
嘿 我不会让任何人带走你的
Hey. I would never let anyone take you.
真的吗 我要记得没错 你刚回来而已
Really? Because last I checked you just got back.
然后我厌倦了感到无助
And I am tired of feeling helpless.
不能够...有力量
Not able to... "not able."
等会儿 谁说的
Wait, who ever said that?
异种 所有人都这么说
The Fae! Everybody!
总在提醒我
Always reminding me;
我很弱 易受伤害 我是个负担
that I'm weak and I'm vulnerable and I'm a liability
还是个贼 还有 我亲了戴森
and a thief and... I kissed Dyson.
- 什么 - 我亲了戴森
- What? - I kissed Dyson.
而最糟的是 我觉得我只想亲黑尔
And the worse part is that, I think I only really want to kiss Hale.
我觉得我... 爱... 喜欢他
I think I... love... like him.
也许吧 我也不知道 我只是很孤单
Maybe? I don't even know. I'm just alone.
不 你不孤单肯吉 你还有我呢
No, you are not alone, Kenzi. You have me.
我有你 我拥有全部的你
I have you... I have all of you...
但当事情发生的时候
but when it comes down to it
我根本就没在你心里 对吗
... I don't really have any of you. Do I?
你抛弃过我 波 如果你又走了怎么办
You left me, Bo. What if you go again?
我曾很孤单
I was alone.
我哪儿都不属于
I belonged nowhere.
不管我多努力 我还是不是你们的一员
As hard as I try, I'm just not one of you.
查姆拉细枝
Zamora Twigs.
从特里克那偷东西 亲戴森
Stealing from Trick. Kissing Dyson.
我都不知道还能发生什么了
I don't even know what is happening anymore.
- 波... - 所有那些我
- Bo... - And of all the things
想不通的事... 我从来没觉得会是你干的
I'm in the dark about... I never thought it would be you.
这事还没完
We're not done.
- 你好 戴森 - 塔米辛和你在一起吗
- Hello Dyson. - Is Tamsin with you?
没有 我困在劳伦家了 和肯吉一起
No, I've been stuck at Lauren's. With Kenzi.
怎么了
What happened?
不知道 我想是我跟她急了 她就走了
I don't know, I guess I snapped at her. She took off.
什么
What?
她还只是个孩子 她连怎么扭屁股都还不会
She's just a baby, she doesn't even know how to twerk yet!!
是啊 她还突然看起来很像我的老搭档
Yeah, well she also suddenly looks like my old partner
总在午餐时间跟赫鲁安乱搞 我来找你们
who used to bang Hydras over lunch. I'm coming to you.
你在马西莫家还看见我们中的谁了
What else of ours did you see at Massimo's?
杰拉尔丁
Geraldine.
我的梳子 扔枕头
My hairbrush. Throw pillows.
等会儿...你给塔米辛用你的梳子了
Wait... you used your brush on Tamsin.
如果她看见她的头发在里面怎么办
What if he saw her hair in it?
不会的
No, girl doesn't shed a single lock.
是 但是他是德鲁伊教员
Yeah, but he's a druid,
他还是可以侦查她的油脂
he still could have detected her oils.
而且 他的强盗看见了你的金发的姑娘
Plus, his robber saw a blonde girl.
他知道她还活着
He knows she's alive.
是啊 很明显瓦科基里的头发相当有价值
Yeah, and apparently Valkryie hair is mad valuable.
马西莫不想让我们死
Massimo didn't want us dead.
不 他想让我们困惑
No, he wanted us distracted.
那样他就可以去追求他真正想要的了
So he could go after what he really wants.
追他想要的人
Who he really wants.
- 我一个人去 - 不不不 波
- I'm going alone. - No, no, no Bo...
- 你该等着戴森- 你们很亲密 对吗
- Wait for Dyson. - You guys are close, right?
嗨 塔米辛
Hi Tamsin.
你怎么知道我叫什么
How do you know my name?
你当然不记得我了
Of course you don't remember me.
但在另一段人生中 我们很亲密
But in another life, we were super close.
看见了吗
You see?
肯吉和波给我打电话了
Kenzi and Bo called me.
她们想让我来接你
Wanted me to come pick you up.
你认识她们吗
You know them?
我们可是永远的好朋友
We are best friends forever.
你是来帮我的 是吗 因为我很可怕
You're here to help me aren't you? It's because I'm hideous?
你很完美
You're perfect.
- 为什么你把我捆起来 - 为了保护大家
- Why you tie me up? - To protect everyone.
等你变成真正的自己的时候
For when you turn into your true self.
真正的自己
Ow. My true self?
嗯 一个魔鬼
Uh-hunh. A monster.
我有麻烦了吗
Am I gonna be in trouble?
亲爱的 你就是个麻烦
Oh honey, you are trouble.
你一直在和异种两面派玩过家家
You've been playing house with the Ambiguously Fae Duo.
波是不结盟的 肯吉是临时的
Bo's unaligned. Kenzi's temp.
但你 你才是真正重要的
But you, you are the real deal.
因为我是黑暗派的吗
Because I'm Dark?
正是 你是坏人
Exactly! You're bad.
哦 不 它流淌在你的血液里
Oh no, it's in your blood.
而你变成一个杀手
And it's only a matter of time before you
只是时间问题
become a killer.
这就是为什么你需要我
And that is why you need me.
我杀人吗
I kill people?
你曾试图杀波 我帮了你
You tried to kill Bo. I helped you.
我们是一伙的
We're a team!
难怪波那么讨厌我
That's why Bo hates me.
慢慢习惯吧 因为我们这类人
Get used to it. 'Cause people like us?
我们注定孤独死去
We die alone.
瞧瞧这头发
Look at that hair.
太美了 太有光泽了
It's so fine. It's so young.
我已经等了很久了 现在终于是我的了...
I've waited for this for so long. Now it's finally mine...
唯一能得到年轻瓦科基里的头发...
and the only way to obtain a young Valkyrie's hair...
方法就是把它们剃掉
is to make it fall out willingly.
永远不要剪掉女人不想剪的头发
Never give a woman a hair cut she doesn't want.
你不该在这
You need to go.
因为我要干掉你
'Cause I'm over you.
放开她
Stop. Release.
看好了
Witness.
- 我了个去  - 又出现个新的
- Holy shit. - That's new.
不是新的 是重生
Not new. Reborn.
你的长老患的是一种海绵状的脑病
Your Elder is suffering from a form of spongiform encephalopathy.
消化后的结果表明他一直在吃
The digestive results show that he's been feeding off
本族 有血缘关系的亲属
his own kind, blood relatives.
他要疯了
He's going Mad Fae.
对待这种病的疗法
Course of treatment: Oh,
我不知道 也许要停止一下这样的乱伦
I don't know, maybe lay off the incest a little bit.
你不需要绑架我来解决问题
You didn't need to kidnap me to figure this out.
你只需要用你的大脑好好想想就行
You just needed to use your brain for once.
因为...这是一个孩子的游戏
Because this... is child's play!
接下来是这样
So here's what's gonna happen.
我同意去治疗你那恶心的哥哥
I'm gonna agree to treat your disgusting Elder
同时你也要在克里斯朵过敏性休克之前放她走
and you're going to free Crystal before she goes into anaphylactic shock
由于你那过时的手铐 让她对镍过敏
from a nickel allergy, due to your antiquated handcuffs.
顺便提下
Oh, and these! By the way...
这些孩子的游戏
are child's play.
你那不靠谱的女友肯吉...
Your not-quite-girlfriend Kenzi...
教我怎么去撬锁
taught me how to pick a lock.
那么...呃 我通过你那奇怪的测试了吗
So... Hm? Did I passed your ridiculous test?
因为如果我通过 你就能出来了 黑尔
Because if I did, you can come on out, Hale.
你不就是...黑尔
You're not... Hale.
我是死亡语言家
I am a Harbinger of death.
我会乘着被空气保佑过的风到来
I arrive on winds blessed air.
空气你也不再需要
Air that you no longer deserve.
求你了
Please.
塔米辛. 小' T.
Tamsin. Lil' T.
我知道你想要杀他
I know you want to kill him.
我也想杀他 相信我 但是他不值当
So do I, believe me. But he's not worth it.
我来搞定他 我是黑暗使者 还记得吗
I kill. I am Dark, remember?
你根本没有必要啊
You don't have to.
你可以成为你想成为的任何人
You can be whomever you want to be.
你个大骗子 你鄙视我
You're lying! You despise me!
好吧 你知道吗 你是对的
Okay, you know what, you're right,
你和我 在你过去的日子里 我们一直在斗争
you and I, we fought in your past life.
你从来都不是我的菜
You weren't always my favourite.
你用错误的方法把我绑架了
You rubbed me the wrong way,
你呃 本可以是个闺蜜
you, uh, could be a real close talker.
但是我从来不恨你
But I never hated you.
事实上 我认为你太不可思议了
In fact, I thought you were incredible.
那就是爱的感觉
That's what love feels like.
除了我 没有人能和我的室友作战
No one fights with my roommates but me.
现在 到电梯间去 然后闭上眼
Now, go to the elevator close your eyes.
然后把音乐调最大 可以吗
Turn the music up real loud, okay?
哇哦 你看到了吗
Wow. Did you see that?
我是说 如果你认为之前她是最有力量的
I mean, if you thought she was powerful before. Woo.
她只是有了翅膀才行 你知道我的意思吗
She just got her wings. Do you know what that means?
每月都会抽筋 水肿...
Monthly cramps, bloating...
...这就是她的晚年生活
... this is her last life.
所以我的意思是你救了我的命
So I guess that means you just saved mine.
我才不会让孩子干我那肮脏的工作
I don't let children do my dirty work.
特别是在有人在我送了
Especially after someone sends
夜行神龙之后来做他们的事情
gargoyles after me to do their's.
- 什么夜行神龙 - 我也不太清楚
- What gargoyles? - I'm not falling for this.
不是吧 说真的 夜行神龙有着很高的威信
No, really. Gargoyles serve a higher authority.
他们会攻击任何挑战他们权威的人 异种长老
They attack whoever threatened their masters. Elder Fae.
所以我猜我们现在甚至有点...
Hah, so I guess we're even now.
还不够近
Not even close.
那就是为什么你能通过
That's how you got
那个圈而进入我们的房间
into our house past the rim.
你是人类
You're human.
我是德鲁伊
I am The Druid.
好吧 你的绝望
All right, your desperate,
令人同情的人们 你在寻找我
pathetic people, you seek me.
你需要我
You need me.
- 你会尊重我的 - 哦 尊重
- You will respect me! - Oh, respect?
你认为你是人类就可以为所欲为了
You think you can just take whatever you want?
再一次的离塔米辛和肯吉近了一些
Go near Tamsin and Kenzi one more time.
我谅你不敢
I dare you.
但是你是异种 肯吉只是个人类
But you're Fae. Kenzi's just human.
不 她是个家人
No. She is family.
你需要把那个还给我 来做个交易吧
You need to give that back. How about we make a deal?
你没有资格做交易
Oh, you are out of deals.
- 我没有耐心了 - 给我吧
- And I am out of patience. - Give it to me!
- 给我 - 你哭了 就因为头发没了
- Just give it. - Are you crying right now? Over hair?
我妈妈 需要这个头发
My Mommy, she needs it!
我知道她需要我
And I need her to need me.
妈妈的事情 那也要等等
Mommy issues? Get in line.
求你了
Please.
你真是热锅蚂蚁一团糟
You are one hot mess.
话说 热的...
And speaking of hot...
不要
No!!!
咱么谁也不欠了 很高兴认识你
Debt's settled. Nice knowing you.
我一定要得到头发
Now I need to go get it.
不 马西莫 不
No! Massimo no!
我根本有生戴森的气
I'm not mad about Dyson.
- 啥事没有 - 我知道啊
- It meant nothing. - I know.
那个标有我的德鲁伊药水
That druid potion that marked me?
很明显我密封的
That I apparently sealed?
需要得到一个从来没有背叛过我的人的吻
It needed to be a kiss from someone who would never betray me...
- 但是我背叛过 - 不 你听好了
- But I did! - No! Listen.
你和我 我们自食其力已经很久了
You and me, we were on our own for a very long time.
可我们又找到了彼此
But we found each other.
有时我们也会斗两下
And there will be times when we fight.
因为我们是一家人
Because we are family.
但是家人就应该在一起的
But family sticks together.
是的 即使我们闹翻了
Yeah, even when we screw up.
- 我很高兴你能回来 - 我会感到无助
- I'm so glad you're back. - And I'm done being helpless.
我会感到害怕 我们都会
I am done being scared. We all are.
...然后一个邪恶的野兽
...and then an evil beast
威胁要剪去她的头发
threatened to cut her hair
这让那个小公主非常生气
that made the princess very angry.
她开始逐渐变得漂亮起来
And she grew beautiful,
有了一双神奇的翅膀
magical wings,
她扑了过去 把那怪兽叼了起来
and she swooped down, and she picked up the monster
叼着它的耳朵
by his ears,
把它扔到一个很远的陆地上去了
and she flew him to a far, far away land.
去了一个不会伤害任何人的地方了
Where he would never return to hurt anyone.
再不伤人了
Ever again.
天啊 给这个小丫头一点警告 好不
Oh, geeze, give a girl a little warning, will ya.
在这个密室
The inner sanctum.
我认为你一直睡在浴缸里
And all this time I thought you slept in the bathtub.
不 只有在你吃掉所有排骨之后的星期三
No, only after All-You-Can- Eat-Rib-Tuesdays.
你知道你能做任何事情 不是吗
You know you can do anything, right?
- 不对 - 不是吗
- Inaccurate. - Not really.
你没有必要成为异种从而属于我们
You don't have to be Fae to have a place among us.
这有种方法让你能得到更多
There is a way for you to be more.
我来教你
I can teach you.
事关时间 你不这么认为吗
It's about time, don't you think?
是的 完全认为
Yeah! Totally.
- 什么 - 等时机成熟 我保证
- What? - When the time is right, I promise.
看看你这个狼人...让所有孩子都想骂你
Look at you Wolf Man... inspiring up all the kids n' shit.
- 肯吉... - 嗯?
- Kenzi... - Hm?
我把找不到劳伦了
I've lost Lauren.
我想她好像身处危险中 我要找到她
And I think she's in danger. I have to find her.
太感动了
Nice touch.
一点也不像家庭装饰
Nothing like a little home decor with bite.
太拥挤了
Tough crowd.
当然 太湿了 你没有想过用干燥器
Also, moist. You ever considered a dehumidifier?
你从来没有出现在我们面前
You have not been summoned to appear before us.
这里有点事情你必须要知道
Here's a little something that you should know.
没有人召唤我 我想什么时候去哪 就去哪
No one summons me. I go where I want, when I want.
如果有什么想伤害我 我都能...化解
And if something tries to hurt me, I deal with it.
我不会按照你的要求去活着
I don't live by your rules.
我永远都不会
I will never live by your rules.
你想因为你的规矩而杀了我吗
And if you want to kill me for that?
试试看
Try.
对你的建议我们实在没有兴趣
We are not interested in your proposal.
我们的目的是消除那些没有结盟的淫妖
Our intention was to eliminate the unaligned succubus.
是嘛 就在这
Uh, yeah. Over here.
你的内心已经说话了你已经选好站在哪边了
Your blood has spoken. You have chosen a side.
哪一边?
What side?
你是黑暗派
You are Dark.